<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaS on CloudCashflow</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/saas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SaaS on CloudCashflow</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:09:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/saas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 B2B SaaS Examples: Innovative Software Solutions for 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/top-10-b2b-saas-examples-innovative-software-solutions-for-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:09:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/top-10-b2b-saas-examples-innovative-software-solutions-for-2024/</guid>
      <description>Ten B2B SaaS examples that I&#39;m sure you&#39;re going to get some amazing inspiration from. For each of these examples, we take a look at who it was founded by, their self reported revenue, as well as what the product does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 13 Micro SaaS Ideas: Profitable Examples for 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/top-13-micro-saas-ideas-profitable-examples-for-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 09:09:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/top-13-micro-saas-ideas-profitable-examples-for-2024/</guid>
      <description>Top 13 Micro SaaS Ideas - Profitable Examples for 2024.&#xA;That&#39;s going to give you some really good inspiration for each of these micro saas products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Productivity SaaS Startup Generates $50K Monthly Revenue with Slack Integration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/how-a-productivity-saas-startup-generates-50k-monthly-revenue-with-slack-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/how-a-productivity-saas-startup-generates-50k-monthly-revenue-with-slack-integration/</guid>
      <description>How a slack bot makes $50,000 every month?&#xA;You&#39;re going to be learning about an amazing SaaS journey, including how they got their first customers, why they built this product, and how they&#39;re continuing to grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Career in the Age of AI: 9 Lessons from Andrew Ng</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/building-a-career-in-the-age-of-ai-9-lessons-from-andrew-ng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/building-a-career-in-the-age-of-ai-9-lessons-from-andrew-ng/</guid>
      <description>This article summarizes some interesting points from the book How to Build Your Career in AI by Andrew Ng.&#xA;In How to Build Your Career in AI, Andrew Ng, one of the leading experts in artificial intelligence, shares valuable lessons not only for those in the AI field but for anyone looking to develop their career in the digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 0 To 100 Customers: How To Grow Your (Micro) SaaS From Scratch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/from-0-to-100-customers-how-to-grow-your-micro-saas-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/from-0-to-100-customers-how-to-grow-your-micro-saas-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Launching a SaaS business is exhilarating, but the journey from zero to your first 100 customers can be daunting. In this article I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to get your 1st - 100 SaaS customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Code Startups: 3 Success Stories Making Over $1M In Revenue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/no-code-startups-3-success-stories-making-over-1m-in-revenue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/no-code-startups-3-success-stories-making-over-1m-in-revenue/</guid>
      <description>Entrepreneurs are increasingly turning to no-code platforms to build profitable startups without extensive technical knowledge. These tools have democratized app development, allowing founders to quickly bring their ideas to market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Zero-Cost Business Ideas to Start Your Venture Today</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/3-zero-cost-business-ideas-to-start-your-venture-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/3-zero-cost-business-ideas-to-start-your-venture-today/</guid>
      <description>You are not going to get rich renting out your time. You must own a piece of a business to gain your financial freedom - Naval Ravikant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SaaS Content Marketing: 3 Principles To Get More Organic SaaS Leads Fast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/saas-content-marketing-3-principles-to-get-more-organic-saas-leads-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/saas-content-marketing-3-principles-to-get-more-organic-saas-leads-fast/</guid>
      <description>Content marketing is one of the best ways to generate organic quality leads for your SaaS business. When a potential buyer consumes your content online, they&amp;rsquo;re 75% more likely to actually buy from you, assuming it&amp;rsquo;s quality content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Choose a Name for Your Business, Startup, Brand, Product In 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/how-to-choose-a-name-for-your-business-startup-brand-product-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 09:09:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/how-to-choose-a-name-for-your-business-startup-brand-product-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>When you start a new business, picking a name can be an agonizing process. It actually kind of always is an agonizing process because it&amp;rsquo;s so final.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 6 Profitable Micro SaaS Ideas for Entrepreneurs in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/top-6-profitable-micro-saas-ideas-for-entrepreneurs-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/top-6-profitable-micro-saas-ideas-for-entrepreneurs-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>In 2024, the SaaS landscape continues to evolve, offering entrepreneurs new opportunities to create niche solutions that address specific pain points. Micro SaaS businesses, with their focused approach and lower overhead, are becoming increasingly popular for solo founders and small teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step By Step To Create An Minimum Viable Product (MVP) In 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/step-by-step-to-create-an-minimum-viable-product-mvp-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/step-by-step-to-create-an-minimum-viable-product-mvp-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a startup founder with a product idea, but no clue what to do next.&#xA;Or maybe your next steps are to sit in your basement and build for months, because that&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s comfortable for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proven Strategies to Land Your First 100 SaaS Customers Fast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/proven-strategies-to-land-your-first-100-saas-customers-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/proven-strategies-to-land-your-first-100-saas-customers-fast/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am talking about how to get your first 100 customers for your SaaS product. I am going to be offering up actionable strategies and tactics on how you can get this done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro SaaS Products: Are They Actually Profitable In 2024?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/micro-saas-products-are-they-actually-profitable-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 09:09:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/micro-saas-products-are-they-actually-profitable-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I look at Microsaas products and I answer the question, are they actually profitable? Stick around until the end, where I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about the place I would go to find almost endless inspiration for new Microsaas ideas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Marc Lou Makes $1,753/day as a Solopreneur: What He’s Not Telling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/how-marc-lou-makes-1753/day-as-a-solopreneur-what-hes-not-telling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 09:09:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/how-marc-lou-makes-1753/day-as-a-solopreneur-what-hes-not-telling/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I&#39;ll summarize how Marc Lou is making $1,500 a day.&#xA;After spending hours in his YouTube channel, Twitter account, business websites, newsletter and interviews, everything I&#39;ve seen from how he gets killer ideas, how he builds startups and days, how he gets free visitors, how he actually makes his money, and the truth he&amp;rsquo;s not telling us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Micro SaaS Examples That Will Surprise You</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/10-micro-saas-examples-that-will-surprise-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/10-micro-saas-examples-that-will-surprise-you/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll be going over 10 different micro SaaS examples. You&#39;re looking for inspiration, you want to see the competition that&amp;rsquo;s out there, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to find these micro saas products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Lessons I Learned after Building A Micro-SaaS Side Hustle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/5-lessons-i-learned-after-building-a-micro-saas-side-hustle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/5-lessons-i-learned-after-building-a-micro-saas-side-hustle/</guid>
      <description>I built three apps that makes $8K a month of completely passive income. I literally haven’t touched it in probably three months now. In this article, I’m going to be telling you everything that I learned from growing and building this app so that you can learn how to hopefully do the same for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Micro SaaS Ideas To Build in 2024 Before Someone Else Does</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/8-micro-saas-ideas-to-build-in-2024-before-someone-else-does/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/8-micro-saas-ideas-to-build-in-2024-before-someone-else-does/</guid>
      <description>As we dive into 2024, the Software as a Service (SaaS) industry continues to evolve at a rapid pace. With emerging technologies and shifting market demands, entrepreneurs and developers have exciting opportunities to create innovative solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start A SaaS in 5 Simple Steps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/start-a-saas-in-5-simple-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/start-a-saas-in-5-simple-steps/</guid>
      <description>Starting your own SaaS company has never been easier. New tools make it simple for anyone to build software with no code. Gone are the days of raising millions, hiring developers and racking your own servers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
